// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is known as the -Father of AI?",
    answer: "John McCarthy",
    options: [
      "Fisher Ada",
      "Alan Turing",
      "John McCarthy",
      "Allen Newell"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the given language is not commonly used for AI?",
    answer: "Python",
    options: [
      "LISP",
      "PROLOG",
      "Python",
      "Perl"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The probabilistic reasoning depends upon?",
    answer: "Both a and b",
    options: [
      "Forward Chaining",
      "Backward Chaining",
      "Both a and b",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which algorithm is used in the Game tree to make decisions of Win/Lose??",
    answer: "Min/Max algorithm",
    options: [
      "Heuristic Search Algorithm",
      "DFS/BFS algorithm",
      "Greedy Search Algorithm",
      "Min/Max algorithm"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The Bayesian Network gives",
    answer: "A complete description of the domain",
    options: [
      "A complete description of the problem ",
      "Partial Description of the domain",
      "A complete description of the domain",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The total number of proposition symbols in AI are:",
    answer: "2 proposition symbols",
    options: [
      "3 proposition symbols ",
      "1 proposition symbols",
      "2 proposition symbols",
      "No proposition symbols"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Face Recognition system is based on which type of approach",
    answer: "Applied AI approach",
    options: [
      "Weak AI approach",
      "Applied AI approach",
      "Cognitive AI approach",
      "Strong AI approach"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Shortening an IPv6 address means:",
    answer: "Removing a group of only 0's",
    options: [
      "Converting 8 groups of 4 hexadecimal numbers into a valid IPv4 address ",
      "Removing unused groups of hexadecimal numbers",
      "Removing a group of only 0's",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the name of Artificial Intelligence which allows machines to handle vague information with a deftness that mimics human intuition?",
    answer: "Fuzzy logic",
    options: [
      "Human intelligence ",
      "Boolean logic",
      "Functional logic",
      "Fuzzy logic"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: " Which of the following produces hypotheses that are easy to read for humans",
    answer: "ILP",
    options: [
      "Machine Learning",
      "ILP",
      "First-order logic",
      "Propositional logic"
    ]
  }
    
];